Guide to the Larry Kramer Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- November 2016 Acquisition, 1960-2012; 20.67; (23 boxes)
  - Correspondence, personal papers, and photographs, 5.83; (10 boxes)
    - Business and financial papers, 1997-2008; 6 folders (Box 216)
    - Business and financial papers, 1998-2012; 5 folders (Box 217)
    - Business and financial papers, 1999-2013; 6 folders (Box 218)
    - Correspondence, 1976-2016; 5 folders (Box 219)
    - Architectural Digest article draft and notes, 1999 (Box 219)
      Includes drafts and research notes for an Architectural Digest article written by Larry Kramer.
    - Clippings and press, 2003-2016; 2 folders (Box 219)
    - Clippings and press, 2009-2015 (Box 220)
    - Event flyers, undated (Box 220)
    - Event planning documentation, 2004-2007 (Box 220)
    - "Forum on Theatre for Public Health" program, 2011 (Box 220)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis newsletter, 1982 (Box 220)
    - Empty CD case for Dawn Upshaw's "I Wish It So", 1994 (Box 227)
    - "The Normal Heart" playbills and press clippings, 2011 (Box 220)
    - Obituaries and rolodex cards, circa 1989-1990 (Box 220)
    - Out 100, 2011 (Box 220)
    - Outer Critics Circle Award presented to Larry Kramer for "The Normal Heart" revival, 2011 (Box 220)
    - Photographs, undated; 4 folders (Box 221)
    - Photographs, circa 1990 (Box 226)
    - Theatrical programs, 2011-2013
    - Lapel pin from the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences, 1971 (Box 227)
  - Diaries and notebooks, 3.0; (4 boxes)
    Includes Larry Kramer personal diaries and calendars, as well as a number of notebooks used to record financial information, addresses and phone numbers.
    - Appointment/daybook, 1960 (Box 222)
    - Appointment/daybook, 1961 (Box 222)
    - Appointment/daybooks, 1962 (Box 222)
    - Diary, 1963 (Box 222)
    - Diary, 1964 (Box 223)
    - Diary, 1965 (Box 223)
    - Appointment/daybook, 1966 (Box 223)
    - Record/address books, undated; (2 folders) (Box 223)
    - Appointment/daybooks, 1967-1997; (14 notebooks) (Box 224)
    - Appointment daybooks, 1997-2004; (5 notebooks) (Box 225)
  - Electronic Media, 1.25; (1 box)
    - Larry Kramer's Apple computer hard drive, 2011 (Box 228)
  - Audiovisual materials, 1.25; (1 box)
    - "One Angry Man: Larry Kramer" Nightline episode, 2001 (Box 229)